[Music]
Hello friends, I Manoj Jaiswal
heartily welcome you to this video. Today
in this video we are going to talk
about the best plan of IC Lord. Yes,
IC Lord has a health insurance called
Max Protect. This is such a
plan in IC Lord in which
you get two variants, one is
Classic and one is Premium. So
you
can take this plan according to your requirement. We will explain the rest of the complete information, what are the
benefits, what are the special features in this
plan, in this video. So stay tuned
till the end so that
you can understand that on
my computer screen where
we have opened the presentation, the first unique feature of IC Lord
's Max Protect Health Insurance
Plan is that it
provides worldwide coverage, in
which there is no co-payment, meaning there is no
capping and
you will not have to pay any co-payment, even if in case you
go outside India and you need treatment there.
Secondly, in this
you will get a committee bonus starting from Rs. 20.  Between 100%
and thirdly, there is the
option of higher sum assured and along with it there
is an unlimited time unlimited option in it
that you can also get unlimited insurance in it,
if we talk about the
basic details then the name of this plan is
ICICI Lord Max Product,
as I told you earlier, if we
talk about claim ratio then the claim ratio is
88.5 but income ratio which means
how many claims came is 91.6, but if we
talk about variants, there are two variants in it,
one is classic and one is premium,
if we talk about age of entry then the
age of entry for adults is 18
years to 65 years, for dependent child it is
91 days to 25 years and if you are
taking an individual policy then it is six
years, if we talk about room eligibility then there is
no limit on the room, you
can take any type of room, whether you want to
take a suite or a suite, you can take it there  If we
talk about refill benefit, then there is unlimited
option in it, that is, as I
told you earlier that if you have taken a plan of
Rs 1 crore, it gets exhausted, then it will get
automatically refilled again, then if we
talk about emergency road ambulance, then it
is covered at maximum hospitalization of Rs 100, there is
guaranteed cumulative bonus as
I told you, no claim bonus which is
at Rs 20 and maximum 100% and whatever reduction will happen,
it will not happen at all, if in these cases, any
claim comes in future, day treatment
is covered in it up to sum amount and there domus
treatment is also covered as per sum amount,
if we talk about AYUSH treatment, then
that too is given full coverage, that means no
condition has been put in it
that there is any limit, you can cover that also up to sum
amount, modern treatment
is also covered up to sum amount, maximum
you get coverage of Rs 1 crore in it and
if we talk about pre and post
hospitalization, then pre and post
Hospitalization is 60 days, pre and
post is 180 days but related to the same illness. On the other hand,
if we talk about further e-
consultation, then e-consultation is unlimited
times, which means if we understand that you can
use e-consultation as many times as you want, there is no
limit on it.
Bariatric surgery will also be
covered for a limited time and OPD is not covered under it, which
means OPD is covered, which means if you
want to go for consultation physically, then that
is not covered. Deduct option is also
not available under it. On the other hand, if we
talk about zonal payment, then zonal
payment means that in case you are
in Delhi or in rural area or
in main city, then there will be a difference in your premium.
If you are in Delhi, then the
premium for Delhi will be different and if you are
living in any outer area from Delhi, that
means you are living in Uttar Pradesh
or in any village, then your
premium there will be different. Waiting period is the
most important part.
If we talk about the initial waiting
period of any policy, then the initial waiting period is
when you take a fresh policy, then in
that case it is 30 days, but yes,
your accident will be covered on the first day. If there is
any specific disease, the
exclusion for that is two years. If you have to undergo any
biopsy surgery, then there is a
waiting period of 3 years. If there is any pre-existing
condition, that means you have any pre-existing disease,
you will have to declare it. If you ever
take health insurance, then the waiting
period for it will be 4 years.
Talking about variants, one variant is the
home care treatment which is classic, there is a
premium in it, if you are taking home care treatment then it will
not be covered in classic, it will be
covered under the premium,
premium is an option, it will be covered under the premium
and will be covered ₹1 lakh. World
wide coverage which is classic will be
covered under both classic and premium and will be covered up to the
amount installed, maximum up to ₹1 crore.
If we talk about claim protector, then
claim protector also  It is covered
under both the options and if we talk about
preventive health checkup, then it
is not covered under Classic but it
is covered under premium which will be maximum Rs. 00 per year.
If we talk about emergency air ambulance, then it is
not covered under Classic but it will be
covered under premium up to some extent.
Now if we talk about
changing the room category, then this option is
not available in it, that means when you are taking the policy, then
if you want to
downgrade your room limit
to a single private room so that
your premium gets reduced, then
that option is available in Classic but
this option is not available under premium. So by
coming here the presentation is
complete but now let us understand
this plan with an example by
going to the IIC Lord website. Now
we have come to the IIC Lord website
where we have opened Max Protect.
We have taken that there are two adults
whose date of birth we take for foreign
Example 171 19 97 and let's take the other one
199 now here we have to enter email ID and mobile
number so we enter the office number
and email ID because that is a
verification of the company now
I have entered a daily pin code and
entered the name Manoj Jaiswal now if we enter the get code then you will
understand what premium we have to take here
all the conditions are checked here and
here it is running a bit slow on the website
now as soon as we go ahead on Lord's
website we are moving ahead and here
you will see the premium in front of you here the
premium has come 2666 premium is coming
now what is it any where cashless cashless any
hospital is written clear if we move ahead it is
inpatient treatment
means whatever I told you there everything
is covered in it now see
what is written sum is shown premium here p option sum is
shown is written crore crore 3 crore f
crore 10 crore unlimited and if you change it to
classic  If you go there, there
is an option of Classic. Under Classic, the condition sum
is same in both, but the
premium coming under Classic is 1917 and
under premium it is
2666. If I make this unlimited, then the
unlimited premium coming is 3456, meaning
unlimited for two adults.
We have put the coverage under this. Further, if
you want to see the pin code of the hospital, which
is covered, room rent, day care
procedure, you will
get the details of everything here, which we have
told you as it is. If you understood everything, then
you will come here and continue. But yes,
keep one thing in mind, whatever premium is being
shown to you here, you will see GST inside it, so
here GST will be
extra. So, in this way,
you can see for yourself
what your premium is coming and
what premium will be according to your family. So,
here in this way, you can complete your policy.
Information in which we
understood about ICICI Lombard's Max
Protect Plan, so how did you like this plan
or if you have any feedback, then please
comment in the comment box. Otherwise, if
you want to compare this plan with any other plan, then
please
mention it in the comment box. Otherwise, if you
liked the video, then do not forget to like the video and
share it with as many people as possible so that
they keep getting information about this plan.
Otherwise, if you have
not yet subscribed to the channel or you have come to this channel for the
first time, then please do
not forget to subscribe to the channel by pressing the red button given below
because we keep bringing such videos
for you from time to time. Finally, thank
you very much for watching this video completely.
[Music]